pongoresume.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Pongo

1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting Pongo. We really value your privacy, and we wrote this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect and use your personal information in plain English. This Privacy Policy (or “Agreement”) is a binding agreement and you must agree to the terms within it and adhere to them at all times. 

2\. Personal Information We Collect

The type of information we collect is similar for each of our users and includes many things. But first, please know that our Site and Service is only meant for those who are eligible to use it based on our Terms of Service, which is incorporated into this Agreement. 

To use our Site you will be providing your name, phone, email, address and credit card information. In addition to this general data we may also require specific information about your work history and job profile in order to provide our suite of services to you. 

3\. Non-Personal Information We Collect

We may collect information about you that is not personal information. When you access our web site, we may collect such things as your IP address, browser, operating system, and other general information about our visitors. This information, on its own, cannot usually be used to identify you. 

4\. Use of Information

We may use your information: 

  * To enhance or improve user experience, our web site, or our service.
  * To send emails about our site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send emails about our web site and other products, news, or updates. These emails will only be about us, Pongo.
  * To generate resumes, cover letters, follow-up letters, thank yous, etc. and reminders.
  * On the telephone, to assist you in a variety of ways with your job search - resumes, cover letters, interview help, etc.
  * Credit card processing.
  * Analytics.

Other than as described in this Agreement, we use your information to provide maintenance and enhancements, as well as auto updates to our Service. We may also collect information to determine compatibility with new technology. Any other use of your information will be described in this Privacy Policy. We may also hire third parties to help us in the development of our Site or enhancement of our Platform. These third parties will be bound by these practices and will understand that they may only use the information for internal purposes and only for the specific purpose that they are providing to us. 

Notable third parties that may receive access to various aspects of the information you share with us include, but are not limited to, the following: 

  * Data Analytics Providers
  * Search Engine Marketing Software Providers and Consultants
  * Credit Card Processing Provider
  * Live Chat Software
  * Bulk Email Software Providers
  * Professional Resume Writers

If you contact us via email we may also save any correspondence that you send to us. We may then use that information to contact you to answer questions or respond to customer support inquiries. We may also use this information to respond to press and media inquiries as well. 

Finally, we may use the information we collect for internal reporting services. This helps us to develop new products, services, and to enhance existing ones. 

5\. Cookies

We use cookies for a number of purposes. These purposes include saving your preferences and tracking advertisements. 

Because cookies are necessary to distinguish you from other users, we recommend leaving your cookies enabled in your browser. 

6\. Third Party Web sites

We may link to third party web sites from our own web site. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, these third party web sites or their use of your personal information. We recommend that you review their privacy policies and other agreements governing your use of their web site. 

7.1 Third Party Analytics

As described in Section 4 above, we use third party services to collect, store, and analyze information about our users. 

7.2 APIs

We may have APIs to allow you to interface with other services such as our job search tool. Please know that other web sites may have different privacy standards. We recommend that you acquaint yourself with their standards accordingly if you are concerned about API integration. 

8\. Third Party Access to Your Information

We may allow third parties to access, maintain, or otherwise use your information for purposes that we deem conducive to improving our Site and Service. For example, we use a third party hosting provider to host our Site’s data. We strive to always contract with reputable providers, but it is impossible to be one hundred percent sure of the reliability of a third party over whom we do not have complete control. As such, you hereby agree that we are not liable for any privacy breaches that may occur as a result of the actions of third parties. 

9\. Law Enforcement

We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. 

10\. Security of Your Information

At Pongo, we are diligent about keeping your personal information and credit card data secure. Take data encryption for example. We don't stop at using SSL Certificates. We are PCI Compliant and the data center where our servers are housed is SAS 70 Type I & II Compliant and meets or exceeds the criteria for Type I & Type II SAS Compliance. But, because nothing in life is ever foolproof, we recommend that you take every precaution necessary to enhance your own computer's privacy measures, including anti-virus software and firewalls. 

11\. California Online Privacy Protection Act

Individuals from California may use our web site. We fully comply with California’s privacy legislation as it relates to dealing with California’s residents. If you have any questions about your rights under this Privacy Policy, please contact us for more information. 

12\. Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on our web site in place of the old version. We recommend that you periodically refer back to this Privacy Policy to make yourself aware of the newest amendments. 

13\. COPPA

We do not allow people to use our Site, Service, or be a referral if they are under the age of contractual capacity, which is usually eighteen years old, and therefore the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act’s provisions, or its equivalent in your jurisdiction, is not relevant. If we discover that someone under the legal age is using our Site or Program then we may terminate their access, delete any information they have provided except we may store some information for a reasonable time in order to protect others or ourselves.
